var questions = [
    {
        "question" : "Whats the capital of Columbia?",
        "answer1" : "Cairo",
        "answer2" : "Bogota",
        "answer3" : "Baku",
        "answer4" : "Praia",
        
        "answer" : 2
    },
    
    {
        "question" : "Whats the capital of Bolivia?",
        "answer1" : "Sofia",
        "answer2" : "San Jose",
        "answer3" : "Bengui",
        "answer4" : "La Paz",
        
        "answer" : 4
    },
    
    {
        "question" : "Whats the capital of Iran?",
        "answer1" : "Tehran",
        "answer2" : "Baghdad",
        "answer3" : "Tel Aviv",
        "answer4" : "Astana",
        
        "answer" : 1
    },
    
    {
        "question" : "Whats the capital of Georgia?",
        "answer1" : "Baku",
        "answer2" : "Tbilisi",
        "answer3" : "Male",
        "answer4" : "Wellington",
        
        "answer" : 2
    },
    
    {
        "question" : "Whats the capital of Nepal?",
        "answer1" : "Rabat",
        "answer2" : "Abuja",
        "answer3" : "Kathmandu",
        "answer4" : "Oslo",
        
        "answer" : 3
    },
    
    {
        "question" : "Whats the capital of Niger?",
        "answer1" : "Niamey",
        "answer2" : "Belfast",
        "answer3" : "Chisinau",
        "answer4" : "Dakar",
        
        "answer" : 1
    },
    
    {
        "question" : "Whats the capital of Iceland?",
        "answer1" : "Reykjavik",
        "answer2" : "Amman",
        "answer3" : "Maseru",
        "answer4" : "Riga",
        
        "answer" : 1
    },
    
    {
        "question" : "Whats the capital of Kyrgyzstan?",
        "answer1" : "Port au Prince",
        "answer2" : "Ashgabat",
        "answer3" : "Bishkek",
        "answer4" : "Lilongwe",
        
        "answer" : 3
    },
    
    {
        "question" : "Whats the capital of Ghana?",
        "answer1" : "Maputo",
        "answer2" : "Accra",
        "answer3" : "Astana",
        "answer4" : "Majuro",
        
        "answer" : 2
    },
    
    {
        "question" : "Whats the capital of Peru?",
        "answer1" : "Lisabon",
        "answer2" : "Lusaka",
        "answer3" : "Kampala",
        "answer4" : "Lima",
        
        "answer" : 4
    }
];